A Neighbor's Deception is a thriller film directed by Kenny Gage.
A woman begins to suspect that her therapist neighbor's offer to free
treatment is not the altruistic gesture it was meant to be.
Chloe Anderson, played by Ashley Bell.
Gerald Dixon, played by Tom Amandes.
Cynthia, played by Cosima Cabrera.
Cheryl Dixon, played by Isabella Hofmann.
Caroline Rooker, played by Marissa Labog.
Dean O'Brien, played by William Christian.
Rape by deception is a situation in which the perpetrator deceives the victim into participating in a
sexual act to which they would otherwise not have consented, had they not been deceived.
Deception can occur in many forms, such as illusory
perceptions, false statements, and false actions.
The tone is intense.